hodesiq.com 2012-05-26

# Hodes iQ - Hodes iQ - Global Leader in Talent Management Solutions

**PRIVACY STATEMENT**

This privacy statement describes the procedures Technomedia-Hodes iQ has implemented for this website to insure the privacy of our customers and visitors. With the goal of providing you with better products and services, you might be required to enter personal information such as your name, address, e-mail address and credit card number. Technomedia has taken all possible means to insure the integrity and security of this data.

To provide you with a personalized experience, Technomedia-Hodes iQ has developed many mechanisms to customize the content of this website to better fit your needs. Some of the content of this website is only accessible to our clients, who benefit from a personalized service. The information gathered enables Technomedia-Hodes iQ to better identify particular needs and to provide our clients with custom made business solutions. 

With the present document, Technomedia-Hodes iQ reaffirms its commitment to insure the security and integrity of the data collected via this website. Technomedia-Hodes iQ does not share, sell or trade personal information obtained via this website and this data will not, in any case, be rendered accessible to third parties. 

Personal information gathered via this website is stored in secured offices, on secured servers which are not accessible via the Internet. Credit card information is used for payments only. 

Technomedia-Hodes iQ reserves the right to obtain information on the location of its visitors to insure the development of its products and websites. This information can be of geographical, statistical or other nature.

COOKIES  
The Technomedia-Hodes iQ website might contain "cookies" to provide better service to our clients and visitors. "Cookies" are small text files, transmitted from the server to the client's computer. These files are used to store information which is used to provide custom content.

EXTERNAL SITES  
Technomedia-Hodes iQ cannot be held responsible, in any way, by the privacy policies in place on websites for which a link is provided or not. Technomedia-Hodes iQ cannot be held responsible, in any way, by the privacy policies of its partners, shareholders or members websites.

U.S. - EU SAFE HARBOR PRIVACY STATEMENT  
Technomedia-Hodes iQ has established a comprehensive privacy program, including a global privacy office and a chief privacy officer, designed to help us respect and protect your data privacy rights. Technomedia-Hodes iQ also complies with the U.S.-EU Safe Harbor Framework and the U.S.-Swiss Safe Harbor Framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal information from European Union member countries and Switzerland. The principles of Safe Harbor compliance are notice, choice, onward transfer, security, data integrity, access, and enforcement.  Additional information about the Safe Harbor principles and certification process can be found at <http://www.export.gov/safeharbor/>.

DISPUTE RESOLUTION  
Technomedia-Hodes IQ participates in the EU and Swiss Safe Harbor Privacy Framework as set forth by the United States Department of Commerce.  As part of our [participation](https://www.export.gov/safehrbr/list.aspx) in the safe harbor, we have agreed to TRUSTe dispute resolution for disputes relating to our compliance with the Safe Harbor Privacy Framework. If you have any complaints regarding our compliance with the Safe Harbor you should first contact us (as provided above). If contacting us does not resolve your complaint, you may raise your complaint with TRUSTe by [Internet here](http://watchdog.truste.com/pvr.php?page=complaint&url=www.hodesiq.com),  fax to 415-520-3420, or mail to Watchdog Complaints, TRUSTe, 55 2nd Street, 2nd Floor, San Francisco, CA, USA 94105. If you are faxing or mailing TRUSTe to lodge a complaint, you must include the following information: the name of company, the alleged privacy violation, your contact information, and whether you would like the particulars of your complaint shared with the company. For information about TRUSTe or the operation of TRUSTe's dispute resolution process, [click here](http://watchdog.truste.com/pvr.php?page=complaint&url=www.hodesiq.com) or request this information from TRUSTe at any of the addresses listed above. The TRUSTe dispute resolution process shall be conducted in English.  For human resources data we have agreed to cooperate with Data Protection Authorities. 

CONTACT  
For any information regarding this Privacy Statement, please write to [privacy@tmhodesiq.com](mailto:info@technomedia.com).
